Finding Aid for the Wallace University School Photographs
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Wallace University School Photographs
1901-1929
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0484
- ATHLETICS
  - Coaches Farrell, Reid Carpenter, Ollie Minton, 1929
  - Basketball – n.d.
  - Baseball Team – n.d.
  - Baseball Team, state championship [framed] – n.d.
  - Football Team, 1902
  - Football Team – n.d.
  - Unidentified – n.d.
- CLASS PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Class of 1901
  - Class of 1902
  - Class of 1905
  - Class of 1925
  - Class of 1925-1926 [framed]
  - Class – n.d.
- HI-Y CLUB
  - Hi-Y Club, 1926-1927
  - Hi-Y Club, 1928-1929
- STUDENT BODY
  - Coeds – n.d.
  - Student Body, 1915
  - Student Body – n.d.
- UNIDENTIFIED